A Finding Aid to the Christine Burgin Gallery Records, 1980-2016, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Client Files, 1983-2013; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; 3.5 Linear feet Boxes 15-18
  - Mercersburg Academy, 1985-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Metzdroff, Gerd, 1983-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Victoria Miro Gallery, 1990-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1990-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - M, General, 1986-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Gallerie Nelson, 1988-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Annina Nosei Gallery, 1987-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - N, General, 1987-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Oresman, Janice, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Karl Ernst Osthaus Museum, 2001-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - O, General, 1989-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Galerie Peter Pakesch, 1990-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Panza, Giuseppe, 1990-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Paul Frederic, 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Galerie Marga Paz, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Perlstein, Sylvio, 1989-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Printed Matter, 1989-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - P, General, 1988-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Regen, Stuart, 1989-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Rhodes, Jeffrey J., 1986-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Ricke, Rolf, 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Rogers, Connie, 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Roos Fredrik, 1988-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Galerie Thaddaeus Ropac, 1989-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Rosen, A. G., 1988-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - R, General, 1987-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Saouma, Samia, 1989-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Satake, Schoichiro, 2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Schöttle, Rüdiger, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Schubert, Karsten, 1987-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Selwyn, Marc, 1989-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Singer, Sid, 1986-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Solway, Arthur, 1986-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Solway, Carl, 1986-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Spirit Photographers, 2000-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Spiegel, Emily, 1987-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Szwajcer, Micheline, 2001-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - S, General, 1986-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 21-22)
  - Galerie Tanit, 1988-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Texas Gallery (Fredericka Hunter), 2000-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - T, General, 1988-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Vila Casas, Antonio, 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - VIART, 2004-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - V, General, 1987-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Ralph Wernicke Gallery, 1989-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Westreich, Thea, 1986-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Whitney Museum, 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Williams, Jonathan, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Witte de With, 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Wolff Gallery, 1986-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Woods, Scott, 1986-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - W, General, 1987-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Galerie Renos Xippas, 1991-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Donald Young Gallery, 1989-2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Y, General, 1988-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 39)